Guide to the Levy Dime Novel Collection 1821-1968 Levy
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Novels (Box 1-83)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: The gable-roofed house at Snowden Series Title: Madison Square Series Series Number: 105 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Other Notes: also contains Rice Corner, The Gilberts; or, rice corner number two, The Thanksgiving party and its consequences, The old red house among the mountains, Glen's Creek, and The homestead on the hillside Date: 1897 (Box 43, Folder 861)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Glen's creek Series Title: Madison Square Series Series Number: 105 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Other Notes: also contains Rice Corner, The Gilberts; or, rice corner number two, The Thanksgiving party and its consequences, The old red house among the mountains, The homestead on the hillside, and The gable-roofed house at Snowden Date: 1897 (Box 43, Folder 861)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: The Gilberts; or, rice corner number two Series Title: Madison Square Series Series Number: 105 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Other Notes: also contains Rice Corner, The homestead on the hillside, The Thanksgiving party and its consequences, The old red house among the mountains, Glen's Creek, and The gable-roofed house at Snowden Date: 1897 (Box 43, Folder 861)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Rice corner Series Title: Madison Square Series Series Number: 105 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Other Notes: also contains The homestead on the hillside, The Gilberts; or, rice corner number two, The Thanksgiving party and its consequences, The old red house among the mountains, Glen's Creek, and The gable-roofed house at Snowden Date: 1897 (Box 43, Folder 861)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: The homestead on the hillside and other tales Series Title: Arrow Library Series Number: 60 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Other Notes: also contains the same works as folder 861 Date: 1898 (Box 43, Folder 862)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Hugh Worthington Series Title: Madison Square Series Series Number: 81 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Date: 1886 (Box 43, Folder 863)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Lena Rivers Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 44 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 43, Folder 864)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Lena Rivers Series Title: Players Edition Series Number: 136 City: New York Publisher: J. S. Ogilvie Date: undated (Box 43, Folder 865)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Maggie Miller or, old Hagar's secret Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 18 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 43, Folder 866)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Maggie Miller or, old Hagar's secret Series Title: The Hawthorne Library Series Number: 21 City: New York Publisher: Hurst and Company Date: [1900] (Box 43, Folder 867)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Marian Grey; or, the heiress of Redstone Hall Series Title: Madison Square Library Series Number: 19 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Date: 1889 (Box 43, Folder 868)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Meadow Brook Series Title: Aldis Series Series Number: 159 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: 1900 (Box 43, Folder 869)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Meadow Brook Series Number: 3 City: Chicago-New York Publisher: Donohue Brothers Date: undated (Box 43, Folder 870)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Meadow Brook Series Title: Arrow Library Series Number: 79 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: [1899] (Box 43, Folder 871)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Meadow Brook Series Title: Madison Square Series Series Number: 111 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Date: 1897 (Box 43, Folder 872)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Mildred or the children of adoption Series Title: Aldis Series Series Number: 432 City: New York Publisher: The Federal Book Company Date: undated (Box 43, Folder 873)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Millbank; or, Roger Irving's ward Series Title: Madison Square Series Series Number: 75 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Date: 1894 (Box 43, Folder 874)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Millbank; or, Roger Irving's ward City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Date: 1897 (Box 43, Folder 875)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Miss McDonald Series Title: The Elite Series Series Number: 456 City: New York Publisher: The Federal Book Company Date: undated (Box 43, Folder 876)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Paul Ralston's first love; or, the Percys of Virginia Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 964 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1897 (Box 43, Folder 877)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: The answered prayer Series Title: The Favorite Library Series Number: 147 City: New York Publisher: The American News Company Other Notes: also contains Diamonds, Bad spelling, Maggie Lee, and Rosamond Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 878)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Rosamond and other stories Series Title: The Favorite Library Series Number: 147 City: New York Publisher: The American News Company Other Notes: also contains Diamonds, Bad spelling, Maggie Lee, and The answered prayer Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 878)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Maggie Lee Series Title: The Favorite Library Series Number: 147 City: New York Publisher: The American News Company Other Notes: also contains Diamonds, Bad spelling, Rosamond, and The answered prayer Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 878)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Bad spelling Series Title: The Favorite Library Series Number: 147 City: New York Publisher: The American News Company Other Notes: also contains Diamonds, Rosamond, Maggie Lee, and The answered prayer Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 878)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Diamonds Series Title: The Favorite Library Series Number: 147 City: New York Publisher: The American News Company Other Notes: also contains Rosamond, Bad spelling, Maggie Lee, and The answered prayer Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 878)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Rosamond Leyton and other stories Series Title: Arrow Library Series Number: 253 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Other Notes: also contains Diamonds, Bad spelling, Maggie Lee, and The answered prayer Date: 1902 (Box 44, Folder 879)
  - Author: Holmes, Mary J. Title: Rose Mather or, women in war Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 209 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 880)
  - Author: Holmes, Mrs. Mary J. Title: Tempest and sunshine; or, life in Kentucky Series Title: Madison Square Library Series Number: 4 City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Date: 1888 (Box 44, Folder 881)
  - Author: Hood, Thomas Title: Tylney hall City: Hartford Publisher: S. Andrus and Son Format: hard cover Date: 1850 (Box 44, Folder 882)
  - Author: Hope, Anthony Title: A man of mark Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 2147 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1895 (Box 44, Folder 883)
  - Author: Horry, Brigadier-General and Rev. Mason L. Weems Title: Life of Marion City: New York Publisher: Frank F. Lovell & Co. Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 884)
  - Author: Hume, Fergus W. Title: The lone inn Series Title: Eureka Detective Stories Series Number: 12 City: New York Publisher: J. S. Ogilvie Date: 1894 (Box 44, Folder 885)
  - Author: Hume, Fergus W. Title: The mystery of a hansom cab Series Title: The Modern Authors' Library Series Number: 176 City: Chicago Publisher: Donohue, Henneberry, & Co. Date: 1899 (Box 44, Folder 886)
  - Author: Hume, Fergus W. Title: The piccadilly puzzle Series Title: American Detective Series Series Number: 40 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Date: undated (Box 44, Folder 887)
  - Author: Hunt, Mrs. Alfred W. Title: The leaden casket Series Title: Leisure Hour Series Series Number: 121 City: New York Publisher: Henry Holt and Company Format: hard cover Date: 1881 (Box 44, Folder 888)
  - Title: A husband's story Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 111 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1894 (Box 44, Folder 889)
  - Title: The illustrated life and adventures of Ninon de L'enclos, the celebrated Aspasia of France; with her remarkable letters on love, courtship, and marriage. Full of beautiful illustrative engravings City: Philadelphia Publisher: T. B. Peterson Date: 1843 (Box 44, Folder 890)
  - Author: Ingelow, Jean Title: Quite another story Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 418 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1890 (Box 44, Folder 891)
  - Author: Ingelow, Jean Title: Quite another story Series Title: Seaside Library City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1887 (Box 44, Folder 892)
  - Author: Ingelow, Jean Title: Songs of seven City: Boston Publisher: Roberts Brothers Date: 1871 (Box 44, Folder 893)
  - Author: Ingraham, Col. Prentiss Title: The brand of the red anchor Series Title: Pirate Story Series Series Number: 1 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Date: 1930 (Box 44, Folder 894)
  - Author: Ingraham, Col. Prentiss Title: Freelance the buccaneer Series Title: Pirate Story Series Series Number: 3 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Date: 1931 (Box 44, Folder 895)
  - Author: Ingraham, Col. Prentiss Title: Freelance the buccaneer Series Title: Pirate Story Series Series Number: 3 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Other Notes: this copy has never been opened Date: 1931 (Box 44, Folder 896)
  - Author: Ingraham, Col. Prentiss Title: Lafitte's lieutenant Series Title: Pirate Story Series Series Number: 5 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Date: 1931 (Box 44, Folder 897)
  - Author: Ingraham, Col. Prentiss Title: LaFitte, the pirate of the gulf Series Title: Pirate Story Series Series Number: 4 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Other Notes: this copy has never been opened Date: 1931 (Box 44, Folder 898)
  - Author: Ingraham, Col. Prentiss Title: Montezuma, the merciless Series Title: Pirate Story Series Series Number: 2 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Other Notes: this copy has never been opened Date: [1930] (Box 44, Folder 899)
  - Author: Iota Title: Children of circumstance Series Title: Appleton's Town and Country Library Series Number: 155 City: New York Publisher: D. Appleton and Company Date: 1894 (Box 45, Folder 900)
  - Author: "Iota" Title: Miss Milne and I Series Title: The Victor Series of Paper Books Series Number: 70 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: undated (Box 45, Folder 901)
  - Author: "Iota" Title: A yellow aster Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 1 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1895 (Box 45, Folder 902)
  - Author: Irving, Washington Title: The sketch-book Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 643 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1887 (Box 45, Folder 903)
  - Author: James, G. P. R., Esq. Title: Beauchamp; or, the error Series Title: Library of Select Novels Series Number: 91 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: 1847 (Box 45, Folder 904)
  - Author: James, W. S. Title: Cow-boy life in Texas, or 27 years a maverick Series Title: The Modern Authors' Library Series Number: 92 City: Chicago Publisher: Donohue, Henneberry, & Co. Date: 1896 (Box 45, Folder 905)
  - Author: Jerome, Jerome K. Title: The idle thoughts of an idle fellow Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 42 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1894 (Box 45, Folder 906)
  - Author: Jewett, Charles, M. D. Title: Temperance poem, delivered before the Massachusetts Temperance Convention, at the Marlboro' Chapel, Feb. 12, 1840 City: Boston Publisher: Cassady & March Date: 1840 (Box 45, Folder 907)
  - Author: Johnson, H. T. Title: Jack of hearts. A story of Bohemia Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 1183 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1889 (Box 45, Folder 908)
  - Author: Jones, Emma Garrison Title: A love concealed; or, Deborah Darke's Fate Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 631 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: [1908] (Box 45, Folder 909)
  - Author: Jones, Emma Garrison Title: Stronger than fate or, on the wings of to-morrow Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 1167 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 45, Folder 910)
  - Author: Jones, Emma Garrison Title: The topaz ring Series Title: The Arm Chair Library Series Number: 109 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: 1904 (Box 45, Folder 911)
  - Author: Kaye, Wilmot Title: The lady of Longbourne Series Title: W. T. Novels Series Number: 140 Date: undated (Box 45, Folder 912)
  - Author: Keen, Herbert Title: The skeleton in the cupboard, being some revelations of a family lawyer's clerk Series Title: The "Weekly Telegraph" Novels Series Number: 62 City: London Publisher: the proprietors of "The Weekly Telegraph" Date: undated (Box 45, Folder 913)
  - Author: Kemble, Frances Anne Title: Far away and long ago Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 2059 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1892 (Box 45, Folder 914)
  - Author: Kennard, Mrs. Edward Title: A glorious gallop City: New York Publisher: John W. Lovell Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 45, Folder 915)
  - Author: Kennard, Mrs. Title: Matron or maid Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 1282 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1890 (Box 45, Folder 916)
  - Author: Kennedy, Rose Title: A pair of gray eyes; or, the emerald necklace Series Title: Waverley Library Series Number: 11 City: New York Publisher: M. J. Ivers & Co. Date: 1900 (Box 45, Folder 917)
  - Author: King, Captain Charles Title: Sunset Pass or running the gauntlet through Apache land Series Title: American Authors' Series Series Number: 11 City: New York Publisher: United States Book Company Date: 1890 (Box 45, Folder 918)
  - Author: King, Florence M. Title: A man of the name of John Series Title: Eagle Library Series Number: 162 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 45, Folder 919)
  - Title: A king and his wives Other Notes: signature? Incomplete work? Date: undated (Box 45, Folder 920)
  - Author: Kingsley, Rev. Charles Title: The water babies Series Title: Lovell's Household Library Series Number: 251 City: New York Publisher: Frank F. Lovell & Co. Date: 1889 (Box 45, Folder 921)
  - Author: Kingsley, Charlotte May Title: Lady Gay's martyrdon or, all for a whim Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 1184 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 45, Folder 922)
  - Author: Kingsley, Charlotte May Title: A little imposter or, a fugitive from love Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 1253 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 45, Folder 923)
  - Author: Kingsley, Charlotte May Title: Love surely triumphs or, an unnecessary tribulation Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 1143 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1895 (Box 46, Folder 924)
  - Author: Kipling, Rudyard Title: Mine own people Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 1909 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1892 (Box 46, Folder 925)
  - Author: Kipling, Rudyard Title: Soldiers three a collection of stories setting forth certain passages in the lives of privates Terence Mulvaney, Stanley Ortheris and John Learoyd Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 110 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Other Notes: also contains In black and white Date: undated (Box 46, Folder 926)
  - Author: Kipling, Rudyard Title: In black and white Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 110 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Other Notes: also contains Soldiers three a collection of stories setting forth certain passages in the lives of privates Terence Mulvaney, Stanley Ortheris and John Learoyd Date: undated (Box 46, Folder 926)
  - Author: Kipling, Rudyard Title: The story of the Gadsbys Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 1499 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1890 (Box 46, Folder 927)
  - Author: Kirk, Ellen Olney Title: The story of Margaret Kent City: Boston and New York Publisher: Houghton, Mifflin and Company Date: 1889 (Box 46, Folder 928)
  - Title: The kiss of Judas Other Notes: Incomplete work Date: undated (Box 46, Folder 929)
  - Author: Knight, Mrs. Helen C. Title: A new memoir of Hannah More; or life in hall and cottage City: New York Publisher: M. W. Dodd Format: hard cover Date: 1851 (Box 46, Folder 930)
  - Author: Knott, William Wilson Title: The adventuress or a tale of Parisian life a romance with a moral-the acme of realistic fiction City: Chicago Publisher: The Stein Company Other Notes: from the French of Charles Aubert Date: 1902 (Box 46, Folder 931)
  - Author: Knott, William Wilson Title: Stolen sweets or W. W. W. and W. City: Chicago Publisher: The Bow-Knot Publishing Co. Date: 1891 (Box 46, Folder 932)
  - Author: Knott, W. K. Title: The viscountess City: London Other Notes: author listed on cover as W. W. Knott; publisher listed on cover as Classic Publishing Co., Chicago Date: undated (Box 46, Folder 933)
  - Author: Knox, Cleone Title: The diary of a young lady of fashion in the year 1764-1765 City: New York Publisher: D. Appleton and Company Format: hard cover Date: 1926 (Box 46, Folder 934)
  - Author: L., M. E. Title: Winnie's hero Series Title: Cassell's Stories Series Number: 14 City: New York Publisher: Cassell Publishing Company Other Notes: c. 1 Date: undated (Box 46, Folder 935)
  - Author: L., M. E. Title: Winnie's hero Series Title: Cassell's Stories Series Number: 14 City: New York Publisher: Cassell Publishing Company Other Notes: c. 2 Date: undated (Box 46, Folder 936)
  - Author: Lancaster, Dorothy Title: Lady Madeleine's pride Series Title: The American Standard Library Series Number: 7 City: Chicago Publisher: The American Standard Library Co. Date: 1888 (Box 46, Folder 937)
  - Author: Larkin, Landy (T. J. W.) Title: Never or "wonder of wonders" an invaluable guide for young and old City: Cincinnati, Ohio Publisher: Specialty Publishing Co. Date: 1902 (Box 46, Folder 938)
  - Author: Lawless, Hon. Emily Title: Hurrish: a study Series Title: Harper's Handy Series Series Number: 61 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: 1886 (Box 46, Folder 939)
  - Author: Lawson, W. B. Title: Jesse James' oath or, tracked to death Series Title: Log Cabin Library Series Number: 6 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 46, Folder 940)
  - Author: Lee, Margaret Title: May blossom; or, between two loves Series Title: The Sweetheart Series Series Number: 280 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1903 (Box 46, Folder 941)
  - Author: Leith-Adams, Mrs. Title: Winstowe Series Title: Library of Select Novels Series Number: 489 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: 1877 (Box 46, Folder 942)
  - Author: Le Queux, William Title: Guilty bonds Series Title: Once-A-Week Library Series Number: vol. IX, no. 13 City: New York Publisher: P. F. Collier Other Notes: in two parts, contains part I and part II Date: 1892 (Box 46, Folder 943)
  - Author: Le Queux, William Title: Guilty bonds Series Title: Once-A-Week Library Series Number: vol. IX, no. 13 City: New York Publisher: P. F. Collier Other Notes: part I only Date: 1892 (Box 46, Folder 944)
  - Author: Leroux, Gaston Title: The mystery of the yellow room Series Title: Daily Mail Sixpenny Novels Series Number: 54 City: Australia, Canada, India, South Africa Publisher: The Amalgamated Press Limited Date: undated (Box 47, Folder 945)
  - Author: Leroy, Marion Title: Geralda's delusion Series Title: The Advance Library Series Number: 69 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: Springfield Publishing Co. Date: 1893 (Box 47, Folder 946)
  - Author: Leslie, Mrs. Frank Title: Are men gay deceivers? The lovers blue book City: New York Publisher: F. Tennyson Neely Date: 1896 (Box 47, Folder 947)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: The belle of the season; or, the false heir Series Title: The Select Series Series Number: 102 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1892 (Box 47, Folder 948)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: Beryl's husband Series Title: Eagle Series Series Number: 358 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 47, Folder 949)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: Edith Trevor's secret Series Title: Eagle Series Series Number: 370 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 47, Folder 950)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: Guy Tresillian's fate a sequel to "The scorned wife" Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 346 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1893 (Box 47, Folder 951)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: The haunted husband Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 227 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1892 (Box 47, Folder 952)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: Her double life Series Title: Eagle Series Series Number: 380 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Other Notes: c. 1 Date: 1904 (Box 47, Folder 953)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: Her double life Series Title: Eagle Series Series Number: 380 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Other Notes: c. 2 Date: 1904 (Box 47, Folder 954)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: The old life's shadows Series Title: New Eagle Series Series Number: 464 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1890 (Box 47, Folder 955)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: Sundered hearts Series Title: The Popular Series Series Number: 50 City: New York Publisher: Robert Bonner's Sons Date: 1894 (Box 47, Folder 956)
  - Author: Lewis, Mrs. Harriet Title: A vixen's treachery; or, Beatrix Rohan Series Title: Eagle Series Series Number: 456 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1906 (Box 47, Folder 957)
  - Author: Lewis, Leon Title: The "Isis" mystery Series Title: The Arm Chair Library Series Number: 106 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: undated (Box 47, Folder 958)
  - Author: Lewis, M. G. Title: Abællino, the bravo of Venice or the banditti conquered City: New York Publisher: John Slater Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 47, Folder 959)
  - Author: Libbey, Miss Laura Jean Title: Cora, the pet of the regiment. A thrilling romance of the love and trials of a dashing young cadet at West Point Series Title: Hart Series Series Number: 41 City: Cleveland Publisher: The Arthur Westbrook Company Date: 1895 (Box 47, Folder 960)
  - Author: Libbey, Laura Jean Title: Daisy Gordon's folly; or, the world lost for love's sake Series Number: 5 City: New York Publisher: J. S. Ogilvie Date: 1892 (Box 47, Folder 961)
  - Author: Libbey, Laura Jean Title: Junie's love test Series Number: 30 City: New York Publisher: J. S. Ogilvie Date: 1911 (Box 47, Folder 962)
  - Author: Libbey, Laura Jean Title: The lovely maid of Darby Town; or, Constance, the clockmaker's granddaughter Series Title: Laura Series Series Number: 1 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 47, Folder 963)
  - Author: Libbey, Laura Jean Title: A master workman's oath; or, Coralie, the unfortunate. A love story, portraying the life, romance, and strange fate of a beautiful New York working-girl City: New York Publisher: Norman L. Munro Date: 1892 (Box 47, Folder 964)
  - Author: Libbey, Laura Jean Title: Miss Middleton's lover; or, parted on their bridal tour Series Number: 14 City: New York Publisher: J. S. Ogilvie Date: 1888 (Box 47, Folder 965)